Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪
[The Sparrow's Gambit]
[مناورة العصفور]
[Episode 18]
[الحلقة 18]
[Case File]
[ملف القضية]
Qingyi,
تشينغيي,
you're still young now.
أنت لا تزال شابًا الآن.
[Lin Wenruo, Lin Qingyi's Father] But your mother and I
[لين ونرو، والد لين تشينغي] لكن والدتك وأنا
are already thinking about your coming-of-age gift.
أنت تفكر بالفعل في هدية بلوغ سن الرشد.
We looked at many options,
لقد نظرنا إلى العديد من الخيارات،
but finally decided to buy
ولكن قررت في النهاية الشراء
the commercial street in the west of the city.
الشارع التجاري غرب المدينة.
You were born there.
لقد ولدت هناك.
It holds our most cherished memories.
فهو يحمل ذكرياتنا العزيزة.
[To Our Beloved Daughter, Lin Qingyi] May your future also be filled
[إلى ابنتنا الحبيبة لين تشينغيي] أتمنى أن يكون مستقبلك مليئًا أيضًا
with happiness and fulfillment.
بالسعادة والرضا.
[The Paramount]
[الباراماونت]
When we were young,
عندما كنا صغارا،
in the orphanage together,
في دار الأيتام معًا،
we spent the most unforgettable times.
لقد قضينا أوقاتًا لا تُنسى.
Back then, you said
في ذلك الوقت قلت
you wanted to create a place
أردت إنشاء مكان
just for the suffering orphans,
فقط من أجل الأيتام المعانين،
a shelter to keep them safe.
ملجأ للحفاظ على سلامتهم.
So, every time I received my allowance from Father,
لذلك، في كل مرة كنت أتلقى مصروفي من والدي،
or rewards for winning battles,
أو مكافآت للفوز بالمعارك،
I would buy a shop on this street
سأشتري محل في هذا الشارع
near the orphanage.
بالقرب من دار الأيتام.
Until now,
حتى الآن،
I've bought the entire street for you.
لقد اشتريت لك الشارع بأكمله.
From now on, let's manage it together.
من الآن فصاعدا، دعونا ندير الأمر معًا.
[Title Deed]
[سند ملكية]
Will you?
سوف تفعل؟
The era of Liu Rumeng is completely over.
لقد انتهى عصر ليو رومينج تماما.
The life of Lin Qingyi
حياة لين تشينغي
starts now.
يبدأ الآن.
Blow out the candle.
أطفئ الشمعة.
Originally, this street
في الأصل، هذا الشارع
was what your father intended
كان هذا ما قصده والدك
as your eighteenth birthday gift.
كهدية عيد ميلادك الثامن عشر.
But later, Wang Penghui snatched it away.
ولكن في وقت لاحق، انتزعها وانغ بينج هوي.
I bought it back.
لقد اشتريته مرة أخرى.
Now,
الآن،
it can finally be returned to its rightful owner.
ويمكن في النهاية إرجاعها إلى مالكها الشرعي.
This is the best gift I've ever received.
هذه أفضل هدية تلقيتها على الإطلاق.
I hope you'll like these too.
آمل أن تعجبكم هذه أيضًا.
This is my entire worldly possessions.
هذه هي كل ممتلكاتي الدنيوية.
Your gift-giving style is quite unique.
أسلوبك في تقديم الهدايا فريد من نوعه.
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪Magnolia petals fly across the sky♪
♪بتلات الماغنوليا تطير عبر السماء♪
Let us out!
دعونا نخرج!
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
♪People gather and part♪
♪يتجمع الناس ويفترقون♪
♪How brave can one be with no regrets?♪
♪كيف يمكن للإنسان أن يكون شجاعًا دون أن يشعر بالندم؟♪
♪I will paint love and hate in the sky♪
♪سأرسم الحب والكراهية في السماء♪
♪Engraving my love for you♪
♪نقش حبي لك♪
♪I roam through this chaotic world♪
♪أتجول في هذا العالم الفوضوي♪
♪Who will guard me for life?♪
♪من سيحرسني طيلة حياتي؟♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
Wang Penghui and...
وانغ بينغوي و...
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
[Memory of Hua Shanshan]
[ذكرى هوا شانشان]
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
Hua,
فاكهة،
from now on, I will be the one to protect Qingyi.
من الآن فصاعدا، سأكون الشخص الذي يحمي تشينغيي.
Rumeng,
رومينج،
have you thought about
هل فكرت في
what you want to do from now on?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل من الآن فصاعدا؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
The revenge is done,
لقد تم الانتقام
but it feels like the dawn never comes.
لكن يبدو أن الفجر لن يأتي أبدًا.
Miss Lin,
الآنسة لين،
may I invite you
هل يمكنني دعوتك؟
to share the rest of my life with me?
لتشارك بقية حياتي معي؟
Don't be nervous. My father is a good man.
لا تقلق، والدي رجل طيب.
He will surely like you.
بالتأكيد سوف يعجب بك.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Sir,
سيد،
Mrs. Chen said
قالت السيدة تشين
the Marshal's residence is built on purity and loyalty.
إن مسكن المارشال مبني على النقاء والولاء.
How can we allow
كيف يمكننا السماح
a filthy songstress to come and go as she pleases?
مغنية بذيئة تأتي وتذهب كما يحلو لها؟
Nonsense!
هراء!
Mrs. Chen? What are you talking about?
السيدة تشين؟ عمّا تتحدثين؟
Wenbin.
وينبين.
Wang Wan'er?
وانغ وان إير؟
Is she not dead?
هل هي ليست ميتة؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
you should call me Mother.
ينبغي عليك أن تناديني أمي.
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪Magnolia petals fly across the sky♪
♪بتلات الماغنوليا تطير عبر السماء♪
♪Spring and autumn come and go♪
♪الربيع والخريف يأتيان ويذهبان♪
♪People gather and part♪
♪يتجمع الناس ويفترقون♪
♪How brave can one be with no regrets?♪
♪كيف يمكن للإنسان أن يكون شجاعًا دون أن يشعر بالندم؟♪
♪I will paint love and hate in the sky♪
♪سأرسم الحب والكراهية في السماء♪
♪Engraving my love for you♪
♪نقش حبي لك♪
♪I roam through this chaotic world♪
♪أتجول في هذا العالم الفوضوي♪
♪Who will guard me for life?♪
♪من سيحرسني طيلة حياتي؟♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪